[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Now the interesting thing about him is at the moment, there's no DNA evidence linking him to any other crimes of this nature, not only in his own state, but also now nationally, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "What is your brother to you now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Monster.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Is that what Ariel Castro is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "What he did was monstrous but if we call him a monster, what we're doing is closing the book on understanding how this human being was able to create this prison in his own home and lock these three women up and the horrific acts and abuse that took place.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do you believe his brothers knew absolutely nothing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Could that be at the center of all the depravity that followed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "In that same note he also said, I was abused as a child by an uncle, and I want to give my money to my victims.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you read into this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "What I read into that is this is somebody who may have very well have been abused.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 179, "question": "He never sought it, though, did he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "No --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "NNS", "WP", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "How you would think that may remedy itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "These three girls who -- young women and one of them a girl when she was kidnapped, have been through a horrific experience and they're all I'm sure suffering from trauma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "And finally, is it likely, as seems to be the case at the moment, because of no DNA evidence to the contrary, that he didn't offend really until perhaps his 40s?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I think that it's likely that he offended somewhat and then it escalated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1989"]}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Remember, 1989, he abused his wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Have they broken the law, the Justice Department, by doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "It's possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Department"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "I mean, that's all very well, but the reality is that here you have a real attack on the freedom of the press, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "JJR", "EX", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Let me ask you straight away, are you as appalled by this A.P. story as I am?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Yes, it is very upsetting, but I think, Piers, that we're going to have to see what more there is to this story.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["A.P."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "But that again is an outrageous abuse of their position, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "No doubt about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Final question, briefly, if you don't mind, when you add the A.P. story, scandal, let's call it that -- the IRS scandal, the ongoing scandal of Benghazi, this has been the worst week the president's had, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "This is -- without a doubt, this has been a tough week.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"], "LOCATION": ["A.P.", "Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "This is a bad, bad week for Barack Obama, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "It is, for the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Have you had a good reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I haven't heard from my former colleagues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House", "Senate"]}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Do they want to hear this message?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, I think so, because there are a number of people, both in the House and the Senate, that want to work together and get things done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Should he get the death penalty, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, he's certainly eligible for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What do you think will happen there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Well, in this case, I initially thought that she had a great shot at getting life in prison.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]